Shivani Gupta

Ranchi, Jharkhand, India



shivaniguptaa2@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/shivani-gupta-5745571a5

Summary

I am passionate about technology and love to explore more in this field.

I am an athlete, a Netball Player. In 2019, i was selected in state netball team and we won bronze medal in National East-Zonal tournament.

I love to interact with passionate people, communicate with them and add more values to life by sharing experiences and knowledge that we learn throughout this amazing journey i.e "life".

I feel one of the best companion is BOOK and the best teacher is NATURE.

While exploring through different subjects, I find psychology more interesting and more insightful. Here some of my contribution which i gain through different books and article on it: https://funlrn.blogspot.com/

Experience



ADDRE City organiser

Adore India

Jul 2019 - Nov 2019 (5 months)

Volunteering in a real time environment, Need to conduct surveys, communicate with parents, students, teachers and convince them for sessions. Initially there were no volunteers. I managed it all alone. After new volunteers added, learning to manage team and coordination, within the span of 3-4 month i conducted 25+ sessions in the city including 3 schools and two localities. Praised by organisation's senior, Awarded by stipend and completion certificate

Campus Ambassador

Internshala

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019 (3 months)

Represent the ideas of Internshala to our college, learn social marketing, completed the task provided on time, awarded by stipend and completion certificate.



RV web

Feb 2019 - Apr 2019 (3 months)

I worked there on web development. Learnt basics of web development like Html, CSS, JavaScript and bootstrap. I got two opportunity to work on two project there first one is shivamtech.in in which i work on WordPress and other is their internal project sureshadi.com, a matrimonial site in which i work upon framework 7.

Education



Nirmala College, Ranchi University

BCA, Computer Programming, Specific Applications 2018 - 2021

Ranchi Women's College

Intermediate, Science 2015 - 2017

Skills

Volunteering • Teaching • Team Management • Communication • WordPress